# Lydivette Roldán Front End Developer

Malden, Massachusetts +1 (781) 244 – 0637 □ lydivette.roldan@gmail.com

**𝚱** lydivetteroldan.com

github.com/lydivetteroldan

in linkedin.com/in/lydivetteroldan

## **SUMMARY**

I am a creative hard worker with over 6 years of experience in web development. I have a bachelor's degree in Computer Information Systems and an educational background in full stack development, photography and translation, with a focus in front end web development.

## SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Sass

JavaScript

jQuery

AJAX

Express

MongoDB

Ruby on Rails

PostgreSQL

Git

Heroku

Atom

Sketch

Adobe Creative Suite

#### **OTHER**

- Customer Service
- Fluent in Spanish and English

### **EXPERIENCE**

Jan 2018 - Apr 2018 General Assembly (Boston, Massachusetts)

**Full Stack Developer in Training** – Took part in a 12-week web development immersive course. Learned how to build full stack web applications individually and as part of a team.

Mar 2017 - Sep 2017 Alight Solutions (Hato Rey, Puerto Rico)

**Customer Service Representative (English/Spanish)** – Providing assurance, empathy and support to employees with inquiries regarding health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life insurance.

Jun 2014 - Jan 2017 Freelance (San Juan, Puerto Rico)

**Front End Developer** – Built user experience design wireframes and user interfaces for responsive content management systems in collaboration with remote developers.

Sep 2012 - Jun 2014 String HQ, Corp. (San Juan, Puerto Rico)

**Front End Developer** – Collaborated with a full stack development team to build responsive web applications for government and entertainment agencies.

# **EDUCATION**

**2007** Interamerican University of Puerto Rico, San Germán Campus B. A. – Computer Information Systems